Hello,
hello, nice to meet you.
Much more. Eun Early.
Hello [music] No, everyone. Um, Hong Su-wi. Hello.
No,
[music]
Ike.
We are a little cuter. If I
speak pitifully, I feel like you don't recognize us well. So, I
uploaded it. Myeong-nim, Kwon, and Monk, is
n't it? Kimi and
hello.
Nice to meet you. Completely broke. Tragedies. Nail Jang.
Hello.
Ah, rc. Now, not here, but in other regions.
Dachuk.
Jang. The mornings and evenings are really chilly. Even during
the day, the sun is warm, but the wind is cold.
Rice 1000 units. Each wind blows. It's
already October.
Time flies. At first, it's hard to believe.
Moon, Hwaryeon. Ah, print. Lam.
Hello, you're going that far. Hello.
Yes,
Kal-e. Hello.
It's still up to 28 degrees.
H. File download. It's full. It's hot.
Ah, the temperature difference is bigger than I thought.
Um, but it's gotten chilly in the morning and evening.
A. I
think the
weather these days is perfect for me. It would be nice if this kind of weather could last all year round. I said it
was cold because I was wearing short sleeves, but
in reality, with the current weather, I should wear long sleeves.
If you look at the thin one, it
's a very pleasant weather. It
was 30 degrees during the day. It's not that pleasant weather yet. It's
only pleasant here.
Hello, Bin-nyo. It's
still cold in Chung 4, but
it's hot in hot places.
Hello, Gorani. It's
always around this time of year. It's not
too cold yet, but you can
feel the pleasant autumn warmth.
That's when the weather is so nice.
Every year around that time, I
wish the weather would continue.
There are still a lot of tourists. I
think it might decrease when it's completely winter, but there aren't many on weekdays. There are
n't many days these days. It
hasn't been like that on weekends.
Hello, Amon. It's
nice in autumn, but when I
come to my senses,
there's a wall. It's so cold. The
perfect weather seems to pass by so quickly. It
would be nice to travel a lot in this weather. I
had that thought yesterday. It's a
great weather for outdoor activities, but the
title is still there.
It's too hot before summer. Now that I work on the farm, I
used to think it'd be better to be cold than hot.
Um,
pen, that's 7.  If we talk, we
can't take off our clothes indefinitely, but
why can't we stay awake as long as we
can? Until it's warm, and
if we don't go outside, and
in the winter, I don't know much about that advice, so
in the summer, it's often hot indoors, but we
always have the air conditioner on, so in the
winter, if we just stay inside for a while and
block the wind and put a little bit of southern heat indoors, we
don't think it's that cold, so I
thought it would be better to use it wisely,
but now that I'm
organizing the farm and thinking about working outside all the time, I think it
's better to just endure the heat. There are
many things I can't do right now, so I'm
really worried about what I'll get out of it. Also, it seems like everything will freeze and explode, so it's really a one-shot deal.
Because of that worry,
I think summer is better than winter these days.
In the winter, I don't even think about raising animals.
How can I just celebrate everything now? But
now that he's thinking about it, I have to either tell
someone else to raise them while they're still alive,
or I guess I should eat them as meat.
Ah, I'm thinking about catching them, but I'm so tired. I'm holding on to them. I'm
almost holding on to them. It's so hard to hold them in like this.
I caught one a while ago.
My sister's fur was
just starting to grow back, and
when I caught her, she had
a lot of thick, tiny hairs stuck to her body.
They don't turn it around and fall out, so they have
more hair left.
Oh, and they feed her feed.
Lately, we've
been raising her in her hometown, so she's been eating the same grass as her original ones. Of course, since only one came here, there's a small
sample size, so I don't
know if the others can do it, but that
one
had no breast meat. When
we caught her,
our breastbone
and our shell were attached like this.
Oh, and so,
mallards
eat grass and insects more than they play, and
in this way, they forage for
nutrients and
maintain their bodies.
Anyway, in many ways, their dependence on meat is
good, but despite
raising them almost nonstop, they
had no meat at all.
It felt like they could only sustain life a little. If I were to write down and
catch it, it would be silver.  Anyway, since I'll be eating more feed after catching them all, I
thought I should write down the remaining feed and celebrate when I've finished eating them all, but
no, I can't. Even thinking about celebrating them makes me feel
bad,
so I'm a bit worried.
I know I have to sell them all alive, but it's a bit awkward to
do this, and I'm also
working on the oil factory.
Hello, Lin. Hello,
Leonard.
Nice to meet you.
Eat well. I'm
a bit confused about what to eat for dinner tonight during the broadcast, so
I'm going to
take it off today.
What should I drink?
But I usually
eat rice and eggs with Anchang. In
addition, I've made beef liver. I
don't have the 100 million won you gave me last time, so I'm
using the Korean beef liver refrigerator. I'm going to eat
some flowers and such, but I have
n't eaten them lately. It's been a few weeks, not just
a few days. I'm
trying to eat them again, but I guess I'll have to
eat them again.
Fish is also occasionally available.
Even if I do, things like return are cheap.
The price of ingredients for frost ingredients is so cheap that
sometimes I eat instant noodles or things like that.
Slow-cooked  I eat it raw.
Ah, but this is cheap and everything
is good, but it
has a lot of bones and
it's hard because you have to invest a lot of time eating it. It's cheap, which is good,
but we have to make it a little big.
The price is really cheap, so it's good for later growth,
and it's not just cheap. Seol-i-
tang has
the head and intestines, right? Because it contains the head and intestines, the
effect is huge, and the bones
are embarrassing, and it looks delicious when eaten with the broth and rice.
Ah, but it's
hard to eat all the meat in your mouth, so I
guess you could say it's a bit cost-effective. It takes a lot of effort to eat. I was eating the oil floating on the top, and I ate half of it without realizing it. It was a little bit, but I
ate it once and it
didn't seem like I'd gain weight.
4. That raw fish, that stone, take it,
no, what else can I say? Put some of this in,
put a little bit in, and just eat it with rice. If
someone serves it to me
instead of just rolling the fish meat in rice, boil the rice together and
make it into a porridge-like consistency. It's
really tasty. If you
thoroughly dispose of the fish bones, it's silver.  The
savory flavor inside is amazing, isn't it?
90, but
if you spread all the thorns in your mouth like this, you'll get a lot of injuries this time, and it's very, very bad.
But sometimes you eat like that. It's
almost the same.
Rice hardens and
eggs are eaten a lot. Right now, there are
too many eggs, so I
think I'll see you at egg time, but they're
all like that. In fact, these days, they
don't even come to Jeju. Rather than just
laying eggs, what should I do? I've been leaving them alone. Wait, that's not good, but they've been a bit lethargic lately. That's the biggest problem. In fact, if you look at the eggs,
there are some with really strong central colors, some that are just plain yellow, some that
go far to graze on the ground, and
some that just stay in their place all the time. The
babies move around actively, and the ones that are
promoted
are a dark orange. Oh,
the ones lying in the corner of the room. I think it's the brass story.
Yes, I
think I should give the staff a round of eggs, but there
's no communication. Eggs are laid on top of each other, and there's things like that, so they're clean.
Wow, this is an example. They lay eggs, and
there are a lot of these things, and
there are dirty ones.
Eggs  If it were easy to send it by courier,
I would have just waited and sent it.
Actually, it's not a big deal. You can just
find out and buy it, but you
can't just pack it tightly and send it.
Yeah, it's just one of those kings. They
don't sell it and just take it off and
people around here eat it, so it's okay. They
say it's good for hair, so I'm going to
try it. How about 100 points?
Brewer's yeast itself is a
nutritious
food. Basically, it's a good idea, but it
can vary a lot depending on the processing method. You can
think of it as something with a lot of protein and a lot of vitamin P, but
for some reason, it's good for hair. It's
not 100.5. It's
usually a game. It contains vitamin B complex,
biotin,
niacin, and
other things, but if you
eat enough meat,
there are no nutrients that can be exclusively obtained from brewer's yeast.
So, it
would be good for vegetarians to eat it as a 5-layer zero natural food, but if you
eat a lot of it, it won't
be that bad.  It's not the same.
This is not just about beer aversion. There's also a
separate thing called the nutritional list.
We have a few
aversions that we eat as nutritional supplements.
There's the nutritional list, and
then there's beer mob, S
Wit, and
baker's yeast.
Take the aversion used for bread making.
Each is a bit different.
When making bread, you go to a hospital and make it 00. I
don't eat it often as a mix.
Now, nutritional yeast is
really tasty and
interesting, and it's a bit savory,
so it can be added to food
to enhance the flavor. It's
nutritious, but it also
makes food taste better, giving it a more complex
flavor. It can be used for that purpose, but in the
case of prostitutes, it's really bitter, so it
doesn't fit like a blog. You have to
take it like
medicine. It
doesn't seem to have much merit from the perspective of eating a lot. Do you
think the longer the freezing period, the more 00 separator height increases?
Oh,
it does
increase a lot. Well, Min-hyun, it's been over a year.
After two years,
about 30% of the B vitamins will be gone.
20% to 30% is not a small amount.
Um, but actually, the
real note is that if
you eat [music] little by little, there
won't be many cases where you'll be lacking something like this. Still, it's obviously better to eat
frozen meat from Chimsan sitting there.
I think it's harder than not being able to do it. Rather than having a hard time because I'm just eating
something, I do
n't have anything to start a business with, so I
did this. I think it would be more effective if we
could do it
together, like digging up organic waste and making plans together. But
these days, I
think
that's a lot. Doing everything alone
feels a bit odd.
Living alone like a hikikomori is
becoming
natural, like food. I
thought I was good at it, but I
guess not. Also,
when we're not broadcasting or anything like this, we usually
express milk together in the morning when the professor is there, but
when the professor isn't there, I express milk alone and
experience it alone.
Well, that doesn't mean I want to feel
that way with the other staff members,
so now  I come
here and
pretend to be friendly and friendly, and I
go and talk to them a bit,
but I don't really do that, but
anyway, when I work, whether it's buying or
working on the ranch, I
don't
really
run into other people. And now, what is it? When I work, of course, I do it alone. It's a place with a lot of tourists from all over the world, but I work in a place where a lot of people are moving around, so those people
don't really have that many opportunities to bump into each other, so it's
a bit extreme. I thought I wouldn't be bored, but I
guess that's not the case.
In fact, I don't prepare the anchang rice separately.
If you think about it, what kind of meat was there? It's
not. When you buy raw milk, things like fan meat
need to be prepared to some extent.
There must be meat that needs to be prepared, but I didn't prepare the anchang rice separately.
This is really long. Preparation Ayana. The
anchang rice is from the diaphragm like this, so the
cow is big, right? The
rice is seagull meat. It
depends on it. But it's seagull meat.
If you look at the pork seagull meat,
It's long, right? But
pigs are really small chunks. They
're really big animals. They're incredibly large
animals, so the meat is that much
bigger. If you think about it, you
have to cut it like this to remove the long pieces.
But the problem is that the
grain of the Anchang rice
is long and straight, and the grain
is like this.
Dill is like this,
so it
's not long and horizontal, but
at right angles. You
can think of it as this huge grain. If you
cut it like this because the grain is long, you have to cut it like this. If you cut it along the grain, the
grain is very
firm and clear, so
you can feel it a lot.
Fortunately, it's not a rough estimate. If you look roughly, you
can tell. The
muscle grain of the meat is very clear.
So, the same goes for 1 won Changseol.
When you buy it and eat it, it's
at the peak. Or, when it's sold at a meat restaurant, it's
all sliced ​​incredibly thinly against the grain.
Then, there's another way. It's
New Zealand grass-fed Nanchang rice, and you
chew it while it's still alive in the winter.
If you try to eat it, you can feel that you have enjoyed it a lot,
but now in winter, it is
very short and
thinly sliced ​​against the grain, and you can eat it without any special preparation,
either by slicing it or using
scissors. It is
cheap and you
don't have to remove the fascia or anything like that.
You just
cut it long enough to fit through the hole and
put it in, and then you just
cut it against the grain and eat it, so it is
convenient and cheap, so
yes, I only buy that. These days, I have
3,500 won. It is Korean. It is anchovy meat from a meat box. It is
like cancer. I
like to try a variety of grains. But now,
among the grains that can be used for grilling, the cheapest one seems to be saddle rice, so I
just keep eating anchovy meat. In the
case of the store, everything is good.
Egg delivery is
done by other small farms, and they
send it by courier. It's sweet. It's like a review. * If you
look at the owner's rating, it
is always there at any time.
Okay, a few are broken. A few are
broken. This time,
a few arrived broken. Then that too.  I
think it's a bit complicated, like sending an additional note for each one, or doing a separate inspection, but it seems right.
Eggs,
or even
milk bottles, break. They put them in an icebox and
send them, and the icebox
gets completely smashed, and the milk bottles shatter into pieces when they're
finished, but I don't think the eggs will break. Even if
I package it well, there are
bound to be many cases of breakage during the individualization process,
so there are some ambiguous parts. Since
eggs themselves break easily,
what are some natural cheeses that use the least amount of fruit when making them?
Um,
first of all, heated-pressed cheeses.
Now, the pronunciation that you usually eat a lot is "
jan" (meaning "jan"), but including pecorino, renner
, roman, ho, and
kong tae, you can think of
heated-pressed cheeses as
all being heated to over 50 degrees.
There are many unheated cheeses, but I don't think there are many
that are easily imported into Korea. I'm
sorry, but there are so many that even
Camembert cheeses are
not made to
raise the temperature that much. Soft cheeses don't use
that much temperature.  Let's raise it.
Even if it's not soft cheese,
there's enough shield that doesn't raise it this high, and
most of the hard ones are destroyed by heat pressing 1. If
the temperature rises to over 50, it's the
same as most enzymes. You can think of it as rising to that extent.
India, Sophie,
Ah Jane, Nymph, Nol, cause, mi, An,
hello, member. Nice to meet you.
Egg
4. My eggs aren't that special.
Now that I look at it,
when I raise chickens, the
first condition is that they have to be free-range. You
can't give them a pen. The moment you put them in a pen, the
meaning of free-range is very high.
No matter how
freely you open the yard today and
let them go freely on their own, if
there's a pastor, they won't go outside like that. They
went, and to
maximize the nutrients by eating as much grass as possible and sucking rotten, you have to
minimize the pen's public space or
make it so that they don't come inside much except when laying eggs. I
think that's good.
My eggs are just not that different from the current practice 1.
Since I eat meat every day,
I think it's because of the fat content. Protein and
fat are close to grams, or sometimes even higher. Protein is
twice your body weight, so eating it every day is
fine in the spring.
Do you really need to do light exercise or fasting? I'm a little underweight, but if I fast, I
feel too weak.
Eating about twice your body weight in protein means that I'm
basically doing that. I
have a blog post about how much protein I should consume.
Oh, I'll show you now. I think it would
be good if you read it. There are
quite a few good ones on the bulletin board here.
There's a
post here without a video. If you
look here, there's an article about how much
protein you should eat. When you calculate the amount of protein,
how much protein is
appropriate, and things like that. They
say 27 dinners, so when you convert your body weight to pounds, that's how much
pure protein you should eat.
That's what they're talking about. If you
roughly calculate it, it's about twice your body weight.
It's not quite twice.  But now, I'm
telling you to set that as your target and eat it, so
eating about twice that isn't really a big problem.
However,
it's better to eat a little more
fat since you're underweight. If you're trying to lose weight, or if your goal is to just maintain it, about 1:1 is fine. It's better to eat as much pure fat as you eat protein, about
1:1 is good. Rather than saying 1:1 is good,
about 1:1 is enough to maintain it appropriately. Oh, I can lose weight,
and if I'm overweight, of course I'll lose weight. That's about the level, but if you're underweight and plan to increase your weight, you'll lose weight. And
those with extremely low body fat
probably won't eat that much protein.
If I were
healthy and
weighed 10kg, that's a
little over twice
my body weight. I need to eat a little more than 2 times my body weight in protein.
Is that about 2.2 times? If I
don't eat enough protein, and I
want to gain 8kg in weight, it would
be about 1.78kg. So,
It's good to eat about 170g of protein.
Now, it should be more than double that.
Protein is,
if I just opened 90kg and my body weight is about 190-200 pounds, I should eat 1200g of protein at E41, and if I
eat 100g of protein and 100g of fat, the difference in calories is really
huge.
Doubling the amount of protein and doubling the amount of fat are
different things,
so if you're
underweight, it's
better to eat more fat.
If I weigh 90kg, I
exercise a lot and am healthy and
fit, so I
don't think I need to eat more than 90g of fat and protein.
I always say that it depends
on your energy level and physical condition,
but the point is, it's
not really good to eat more protein than fat.  No, especially
when you're underweight.
People originally eat meat to eat fat, not
lean meat.
Of course, you
should eat lean meat, but now you should think about fat as more important.
Of course, I mean eat enough protein. I'm telling you to
eat enough here.
As I said earlier,
use about 1 or 2 times the amount of protein in your body.
Of course, you might think that's high protein, but
Jongno isn't that high protein.
Now, based on the human white rice, you can
think of it as an appropriate amount of protein.
However, it's good to eat at
least 1:1 to 2 or
3 times the amount of fat intake.
In the direction of pure protein, based on the weight of pure protein,
now double or triple it. It's
not based on 0 calories. They say that
excessive intake of liver can cause problems with the stomach and intestines. Is that
true? Do I
have to take care of it separately?
It's a good idea to take care of it separately, but it's not true that eating a lot of liver can cause problems with the stomach and intestines.
For example, if you
eat a lot of liver and
get on here,  A. As
for toxicity, if you eat vitamin D
and KIT together, you'll have problems.
And if you don't eat any of the MD ingredients and
only
eat vitamin A, it's true that toxicity can occur.
But that's not because the restaurant is wrong, or because
the vitamin is a
toxic substance.
So you don't have to worry about that. If you
eat liver with meat, there wo
n't be any problems due to the excessive copper in the liver. You can eat it without any problems.
Now, eating it together
is a good idea.
If you eat blue fish every day, you
can eat too much omega-3.
Eating a lot of omega-3 is
not that different from eating too much seed oil. In fact, it's
more
unstable, so it can cause more oxidative stress.
Omega-3 is inherently
more unstable than gum and six, and
animal forms in particular are
longer and more bent, which
makes them more unstable. So now,
omega-3s in fish, PD,
JEO DP, etc. are
very easy fatty acids, so
4.  It's not good to eat like that because of science.
The Eskimos who ate so much developed
genetic mutations to adapt to it.
This is
n't something you can see as a way to deal with stress,
but anyway, to
avoid going into too deep a state of ketosis,
eat a huge amount of omega-3 fatty acids and
don't eat elastically like sq or something. If you don't eat like that, the keto-washed
state will
go really deep.
Ah, keton-ni figure 8, 9, 10, if
there's a lot of ketones, our
body
can become acidic like ketogenic acidosis. To prevent that,
Eskimos have a lot of genetic mutations to prevent the ketosis level from going
too deep.
So
sq,
babies
fast and pray,
but if the babies are sick, they are fasted for a month to make them
enter a ketosis state and recover, and then enter a ketogenic state again.
Rather than trying to make them eat when they're
sick, it's better to eat when they're sick.
Fasting is a natural process for animals, too, to
recover and wait for a baby. However, when
diseases of modern civilization strike and the baby Eskimo falls
ill and must fast, their bodies cannot
naturally enter a state of starvation, so they
literally starve to death. There have been
many such cases, and there
were difficulties in treatment in the past and such. I
spoke about something a little different,
but yes, it is
not good to eat a lot of blue-backed fish to get enough Omega-
3. So, Eskimos don't actually gain height. No, they have a lot of wrinkles and don't age that much. It's evidence of stress, dementia, and relationship problems. Sometimes, their appearance and health aren't that good. Oh, it's because they
eat too much music. I'm
still afraid of it, but if
I drink it little by little, it's much better.
The Han River and the goat's better.
Then the answer is yes. But unfortunately, they
drink silver foil.
Ah,
4. Milk and style are more like that. It
seems to be the north and the north.
Babies see golden stools.
Even if milk isn't a twist, I think it's because
they eat a lot.
Milk is a doctor.  Actually, do
n't
drink it right away. It's not that big of a deal, so if anyone wants to drink it, have
you tried compote or something like that? Even if it's not
milk, will it help? [Music] Hello, I went to Coco today and tried the improved cheese 4 that was excreted. I haven't tried it yet, but is it similar to drinking raw milk with kimchi? In
other words, it can't be 100% the same.
Of course, it's a little different depending on how it's made during the manufacturing process. At
least whey is drained or gone, so it's
difficult to expect the health benefits that you can get from milk from cheese.
Maybe if we
drink 1 liter of milk, the
amount of seeds comes.
Well, 1 100 Then, the body
can only do so much, so I don't drink
it like I drink it now, but
I drink it once a day with milk. I
don't drink a can a day, right?
In that sense,
when you eat the same amount, the area in the cheese
and the protein
and other vitamins are different, and
the amount of concentration itself is different, so
in that respect, there
can be a lot of improvement.
But also, it's heated and pressed.  If you eat hemorrhoids, the benefits of
enzymes or supplements that can be consumed in raw milk will
inevitably be reduced.
Arabs often raise their body temperature to around 50 degrees,
and while doing so, they
break down a lot of the body fat.
It's a whole food in many ways.
Green Tester, a large spoonful of new,
doesn't even eat a spoonful a day. Are you consuming it more
often?
Hmm, 1 spoonful is about 15 millimeters, which
seems like a lot.
Eating 5 teaspoons of this amount should
n't be a big problem.
Yes, you don't necessarily need to eat it every day.
If you're eating other foods, you don't
necessarily need to get your vitamins A and D exclusively from cod liver oil.
Western countries, in particular, have
eaten a lot of cod liver oil.
In fact, our country hasn't traditionally consumed cod liver oil, but in
the US and other places, it's a really
traditional thing to eat, and it's possible.
The reason cod liver oil is
a bit
evil, and
it's good to compare it to something. It's
a bit strange when that person says it like this, but
now we have
If children are weak, in the old days,
until not long ago,
grandmothers would
boil carp juice and feed it to them,
saying it would cheer them up. It's
a bit different, but it
's not something we eat that often these days.
But now, similarly,
in Volume 4,
grandmothers would run around,
scooping out spoonfuls and putting them in the children's mouths like this. It's a
big deal.
So, what do children eat? The
appearance of the children growing up eating
it now is similar to traditional food. And now, people who want to eat it are involved. And during World War II and
other times, they especially
mandated rationing. What kind of food is
responsible for the health of the citizens?
So,
it's a natural food for those people. The
reason it's a natural food is because
there are many people who live inland, and in the past,
seafood transportation wasn't as free as it is now.
Even if seafood culture was free, they didn't
enjoy seafood itself.
There was no tradition of enjoying it, and
cooking methods for eating it in large quantities weren't developed. So
now, omega.
There are many people who don't really consume
omega-3. There must be a huge number of Americans who have never collected sea cucumber since they were born. It's not easy for those people to consume omega-3,
so at the national level,
and now grandmothers are
putting in double the amount of Guess loafers and
stuffing them in.
Now, in our country, we
eat well even in March,
and we eat meat with other things,
so there's
no need to diligently eat large amounts of royalties like foreigners do. Do you have to eat twice the
amount of meat to suppress fat intake? You can calculate it by calculating
lean
protein and lean direction. If you
just say whole grain meat, you
can't not eat fat just because you put in 500g of lean meat.
500g of lean meat is roughly
20g of protein. No,
100g is a little over 20%.
Normal cuts
would be around 20%, but now you can eat one or two times that.
Home side dishes didn't work, and makgeolli was good.  You
can try using your rights, right?
Quickly, but that's different, right? If you
leave them at home and eat them, it's
sweet. If you eat them right away, they'll be sweeter.
But if you eat them too much, the answer
disappears, and it becomes a bit bitter. It contains a
lot of alcohol, so
that's probably why you're
adjusting what you
saw. Hello,
is Omega 3 the best?
Um, an appropriate amount is absolutely necessary.
DHA is essential for treating inflammation.
Without arachidonic acid, inflammation cannot be resolved.
2.0 To resolve it from the root,
in that way,
our body needs it. Of course,
and it's not just a lot. It
's an essential fatty acid. It's essential for our body.
Our body can't synthesize it on its own. If you
don't eat it, you'll die. 06.
Of course, you need to have a certain amount, but
eating too much is the
same as eating too much.
Omega 3 is also bad if it's too much. It's
stressful, so would you
brush it off to someone who is safe? If you
have arthritis, it
's good to cut out some vegetables.
Whole grains have high intelligence.  It's good to eat as little plant-based
foods as possible and
eat simply.
Don't mean to overwhelm or anything like that,
just eat rice as a snack,
eat plenty of porridge, and eat plenty of vitamins K, D, and A. Also, eat
plenty of light vitamins.
Including Jeongseon Vitamin 1, it's
easy to eat various nutrients that are safe and helpful like our ninja. The easiest
way to eat them is to eat a lot of this product that wasn't designed.
Here, eating a lot of products is
helpful, so cheese is very helpful because it
contains all the AD Kate.
Then, eat a lot of good-quality,
non-red cheeses.
Now, eating a lot of plant-based foods will
be very helpful.
Hello, Horong,
Haetnim. It's not the 15 milligrams that we usually eat, but
about 672 milligrams. It's about that much,
so I think you
can eat it once every 2 or 3 days.
Can you eat ham and sausage yesterday? The
ham and sausage are the tops, right?
Since they're all thick, just 4
meats are grains.
How much do you eat per day? 5.  You
have to eat a lot.
Eating oily seafood twice a week
will provide you with a sufficient amount of omega-3.
There are seafood without names, right?
Shellfish aren't very abundant, and
white-fleshed fish aren't that abundant.
Oily
things like cod
or [ __ ] do
n't have much oil, so it's
okay to eat those often.
Oily mackerel, ...
If you mean dental health, depending on what my goal is, it actually
stays short even if I don't brush my teeth.
Oh, well, for
cosmetic reasons, I
think you should try it today.
Last weekend, I went to the countryside and was suddenly
taken to the hospital. I was born early this time, and when I
got home, I couldn't do this work and
was resting. I took the maximum
amount of minerals and started drinking Steiner.
But my stomach hurts a little. Oh, my,
Steiner.
Don't drink too much. I do
n't think it will hurt that much if you drink one bottle a day, but
I've heard that many people say that it can be a bit difficult for people with very weak stomachs because it has so many minerals.
8ml. Even in the city, I
heard somewhere that people with severe stomach problems don't want water with so many minerals.
I raised it well,
so it could be the case, but if it
doesn't cause too much discomfort, it
'll be fine.
As for the military police, if you're
only talking about dental health, you don't have to have teeth of reflection
or something like that to become a
politician. Urgent.
Since most traditional groups didn't follow any protocols for dental hygiene, they lived well without any problems.
So, I do
n't think cavities are caused by brushing or not brushing your teeth well.
4.
Fearless beggars,
tartar,
and
green slime in the mouth.
Especially now,
if you don't brush your teeth, it's a
shame. Cavities don't form, but
to protect your teeth, a
lot of dental plaque and tartar form.
Dr. Press
wrote about this in his book. So, even
though people in traditional restaurants have really good teeth,
by modern standards,
those aspects existed for cosmetic reasons.
To solve that, I think
it would be good to take care of your eyes.
On the Saladin Farm YouTube channel, they
talked about the benefits of adding honey and fruit. Can you see that
adding fructose and bone to a can is
beneficial in terms of condition or metabolism? In
some cases, if you continue to not fast,
the pattern
will be too high, and people who are only 5 years old tend to have a lot of cramps.
Um,
that's it.  Paul Saladin Otto
said that he had always had problems with electrolyte loss while playing ball, but after adding carbohydrates, it got better. In
fact, if you are originally healthy, you
don't need to eat carbohydrates separately,
and naturally, I think it's
right to maintain a balance now.
However,
those things can vary depending on how you ate in the past
or how your parents'
diet was. 5. Your
innate health, genetics,
heart disease, or your
ability to maintain a good relationship may be reduced. Or,
the amount of electrolytes in the food we eat may not be as high as it used to be,
so it may not be like a side story. There are various reasons why you ca
n't solve the problem now
if you don't continue to
improve your electrolyte balance without eating.
However,
if the problem can be solved immediately by simply eating carbohydrates, there's no reason not to eat.
Of course, it
may be better not to eat.
Sometimes, the place may be careless, or
there may be extreme situations like cancer treatment, but if
not, everything can come out.  There's
no reason not to always water the fish tank,
but there is something like that. I
don't eat cold presents like you guys always say. It's been several years since I've been in a state where I don't eat them at all. When I look at them, I feel a physiological chill, but my
blood sugar basically
goes up, so I do
n't think that's very beneficial for my body.
Sometimes, when the fruit is in season, I
go and eat some, of course, and
if I happen to find it, I would pick it and
eat it because I was depressed.
But now, you
can only see fruits when they're in season. Of course,
living in a tropical rainforest, fruits that are available almost all year round are
suitable. And people did
n't only live in tropical rainforests.
And it's hot,
right? Flowers don't bloom all year round.
There's no specific evidence that I ate the Steiner on an empty stomach.
Hello, Mr. Woo-rong. I weigh
80 kg.
How much protein per 0 kg of fat is appropriate?
But I don't know if it's right for me to decide. It's
better to set the protein amount based on my target weight.
4.  If you want to gain more muscle and
make it 90kg or 100kg,
then you should eat the same amount of protein as
if you were to convert 9-10kg to 100kg in pounds. If
you
want to lose more rice and make it 160kg, then you should eat the same
amount of grams as if you were to convert 60kg to pounds using Watson.
And if you
want to lose weight, it would be best to adjust the fat content to about
300c, or 1:1. If you
want to gain more weight, you should
eat more than the protein content, such as 2-3 times the fat content, not 3 times, but 2 times or 1.5 times.
And now, we have also considered the square energy level and
lifestyle patterns.
People who just sit at their desks can't eat the same amount as people who go out and move around all day.
Energy sources like fat, like this
25-hour sweet Chico cheese  I
ate 120g and went to sleep, and my body felt like it was burning in the morning.
At the end, my fever cap was 2.95 and my blood sugar
was 55. I
also felt like I was walking on clouds. In
this case, is it right to fast for a long time? I have
n't stopped fasting yet.
How did you feel after eating cheese?
So, if you eat only cheese,
there's not much of a difference from eating the same thing from then on.
And what is fasting for 25 hours
?  It's a bit much to say
that fasting is enough to cause major changes in the body,
but now,
since I'm only eating 4 meals, my
blood sugar level seems to have been high.
Yes,
usually, I can also take hospital prescribed medications. Summary:
Most people have poor intestines. I don't mean
that my intestines are
completely ruined, but even
if they don't, they often have a negative effect to some extent. Is
n't tartar and cavities related?
But now,
when tartar builds up, it depends.
I think it's different depending on the case. I've been taking Proof-
Free Probiotics and
Omega 3 supplements, but I
suddenly had a lot of smoke. It's
been a year since I started taking Vitamin C.
What should I do about this
madness? Is it because I eat a lot of unnecessary Young-ae? I don't know
how much Vitamin C you take,
but it
seems sharp if you don't take it. What? If you
put in a pill, it
will be difficult at least in advance.
Next, Lee takes 500mm. Then, it's too
much.
Most of the trees don't need to be taken.
First, take out Probiotics and
because of that.  It's a step-by-step method.
It would be much better to skip the prebiotics.
There's no special reason for Linksys, and it's better
not to eat it that much. It's
better to eat fish occasionally, not every day.
As I said before,
too much omega-3 is not good.
4.5.
And most omega-3 supplements are
not good for your health.
If you're a street vendor, the omega-3 supplements
just contain a little bit of real oil, and they're
not cheap.
But if you eat fish once or twice a week,
mackerel is a lot.
Then, you can get as much omega-3 as
taking a few capsules of omega-3. But
mackerel contains all kinds of nutrients,
from the B vitamins to
vitamin D and A, and
there are a
lot of other minerals.
Yes, I take
omega-3 supplements, especially in a country like ours where
seafood is so readily available. Of course, if you really dislike seafood, you have no
choice but to take them. But
in a country where seafood is so readily available, it seems a bit strange to buy omega-3 supplements. Your
hair will grow for more than a month.  I
'm losing a lot of weight, and you said I can take 3 batches of o-seol, but will
the time allow me to lose less? What should I do if it's
falling out too much? Should I
intentionally take small amounts of oxalic acid? If it seems to be due to iron oxide, it's better to take
silver oxide. If the symptoms are too severe, then if you suspect it's a moon, it's better to hold an umbrella and control the speed. Can a
villainess drink expensive brain?
Well, as long as you don't eat too much, it should
n't be a big problem.
Rather, if you
eat it in moderation with meals, it will seem raw.
And now,
rather than just drinking milk, it would be much better to make it into yogurt.
Yes, if
you
took 16 pills in advance, you took 6 grams, which is too much.
Seriously,
that's a ridiculous amount.
Of course, everyone is just staring at the front. The
more you eat, the better. Take 10g a day.
Get 20g intravenously. I understand why you
thought that way because many people say things like this,
but it's a
ridiculous amount that you can never even imagine. Uric
acid  Salt is that vitamin C, if
you eat more than a certain amount, it
is converted into oxalic acid in our body.
Even if you eat more than 250 mg, it is expressed as oxalic acid. It is
converted to the extent that it has an effect.
However, if you eat 6 or 1,000 mg of
it every day, the
oxalic acid will inevitably accumulate
a lot. It
can also cause a deficiency in our body's urinary tract. If you
eat it for a long time, it is
too much. I think it is best to stop eating it immediately.
Instead of mackerel,
can you not eat tuna because it is too much? It is broadcasted on 4th.
There is one thing about tuna. Tuna is a
large fish and is high in the food chain, so it tends to have
more heavy metals and such than mackerel.
Life is also sterilized.
Of course, good sterilization is also
good. Now, just because it is
good doesn't mean it is okay. Even
purchased tuna has
many losses.
There is a
video that shows the
reason why it is not good to design an advantage.  I
made a video about glutathione. Even
if you just pasteurize blue tachioni, it's
destroyed a lot.
Besides that, if you give a good sermon, they
say that a good snow scene is good, but
milk is fundamentally a living food. If
you avoid p and red blood cells,
it's almost similar to milk.
Starting with the blood cells inside, let's
put you in 63 degrees Celsius water and
hold it for 30 minutes.
Of course, it's better to hold it for 63 minutes than to put it all in 30 degrees Celsius.
Perhaps the
other person here is also
dead, but each tooth is dead.
Think of it that way.
Also, cows are
confirmed. Most of the afternoon factors are answered. I'm
of normal weight, but I want to lose a little weight.
Why do you consume it every day? Of
course, if you have allergies, you can eat it every day.
[Music]
But I don't think it's a food that helps with weight loss.
But I
don't think it's a food that should be dug up. [Music] I
drank a lot of milk.  I ate a lot of dairy products,
so I can show you with pictures.
Also, when
did you guys have to do this? Since I use Star 2 and Misha, I
had Ultem, so I
bought U+ Box, a children's book, a piece of scullery, a diesel version, and
foam 1 bread. After eating this product, let's
take a look at the people of Rosenthal Valley.
Currently, these people are educators. Since their
bodies are not visible, they are
perfect. Their
teeth are healthy, and their facial features are
perfect.
He is a modern foodie.
Ah, that's it. It
doesn't appear like that in the book. Then, uh,
this is Dr. Percy Ja
2+. He has published many materials in addition to his own book, so the
photos are poorly lit. If you
look at them like this,
there are no strange people, right?
They are monsters.
Uh, this woman is not fat, so I
don't think the product is causing her to gain weight. The
most obvious example of this is
the milk that is consumed, or some
people, like
Africa's purpose of living.  Tribes,
our Masai
uncles
?
Also, below this,
our Masai X people
only ate p, milk, and meat.
Ah, they're really all right and back. The
people here are thin, right?
These people were incredibly tall, but they
were all incredibly skinny.
Here, they
don't have that plump impression, right?
Milk is like Mark. When your body is healthy like this,
water should
be included, but when your body is healthy, I don't
think it's a food that makes you gain weight. I do
n't think it's a food that makes you lose weight.
Ah, anyway,
hello Mint Chocolate Chip. I
have Crave disease. Should I get some vegetables? My
hormone levels
are
normal right now, but it's just a passing feeling, but they say that autoimmune diseases are
incurable.
Next is also a lot of
eggs. Next, if the corpus luteum is no longer found,
it's unwanted.
But
autoimmune diseases
are the fastest and most effective.
In that sense, it's
likely better not to eat it. But now, you can
adjust the dosage depending on your symptoms.
Especially after you get a treatment, this
Whether it's curable or not,
rather than looking at it solely from the hormone level, it's
more accurate to look at things like whether the body produces antibodies.
Hello, I feel bad.
This child
was first told to go on a low-salt diet due to sudden deafness, but I have
a dream that I should do it. I'm against a low-salt diet because my
health got really bad before, but I'm
conflicted because it's Dr. Park's problem. I ruled out a
Buddhist diet, but
after I started the diet, Ahn Chang-hyun, please stop talking. A
low-salt diet can't cure anything else. The food itself isn't a baby-based method.
There's nothing good about a low-salt diet,
so I think that doing something with food itself will
only make things worse.
There are cases where food can help temporarily, but in the
case of patients with severe insulin resistance and high blood pressure, eating salt can make the high blood pressure
worse. Insulin resistance is
already so severe that the cells are
full of something called trifles, and potassium
can no longer enter, so they keep
pouring more sodium into them.  If you
pour it, it will stick to it and not get higher,
but if that's not the case, a
low-salt diet is not as good as you feel.
And if you drain the kudzu water and have hearing loss,
try eating spinach or English for a short period of time.
It can also be because of the disadvantages of salt. Hearing loss
tends to react more in the face area.
Since there is a lot of blood flow to this area, it
could be due to the dumping of thoughts on the head and face, so I
think you can see if eating something like sweet potatoes improves the condition.
Hello, Old Coast. I'm
having a hard time at lunch, so
I bought 8,000 rounds of liver and
am drying it. Should I
take 4 liver tablets? Should I take 3 vitamin A tablets?
How about slicing the liver and swallowing it? Just
like eating it, you just
put the tablets in your mouth and swallow them with fire.
Eating tea and eating liver are
different.
Next, this is just one of the many English minerals in the liver, and
I just really need to take a pill.  The
nutrients you can get from the whole area
are really different, so it's much better to
eat a lot of olive oil itself. If you
really can't eat liver, it
's better to use it even if it's just blown away. I heard they sell
Iberico sausages with beetroot.
Can you eat them? I
don't know what's in them, but they
only contain meat and a little spice, so
of course
you can eat them.
What do you think about supplements like collagen, MSM, and glucosamine that are good for arthritis?
Hello, Gaeko Gaekon.
Collagen can be accumulated more if you eat a lot of meat.
MSM contains plenty of sulfur if you eat a lot of meat.
Glucosamine 2 is good for joints. You have to
think about the principle behind it.
Why is it good for people? If
3 people say it's good for joints,
no doctor will agree. I
don't know who uses clinically obtained data, but there's
no experimental evidence that glucosamine 2 is actually helpful for joints.
And 4. It's common, but it
doesn't soak in water for a long time.  There's no data to
support this or that, and the
medical community and the board members say that glucosamine
intake is
not scientifically proven to help with arthritis.
But
regardless of what they say, there are many
people with severe arthritis and joint pain who have
taken glucosamine and loved it. Their
pain has significantly decreased. They say there's
no evidence, but
many people have actually lost their fathers. If
you look into why that is,
glucosamine
is painful. It's a
molecule that combines with glucose like this.
And now, leptin in our body is a
protein called glucose.
But all of our cells
have alveolar tissues with sugar molecules attached to the cell walls. So,
leptin in our cells can enter and bind like this.
After binding, it causes various problems,
such as a decrease in acuity and other things. As you all
know,
leptin comes into our body and does
something.  Whether it's penetrating through a colostomy stent
or penetrating through the intestines and
entering through a damaged blood vessel, nerve, or whatever, it
penetrates our body here and there
and causes problems when sugar binds.
Glucosamine has sugar attached to its molecule, so
before it can enter our bloodstream and attach to our cell walls, it
grabs hold of the sugar first
or makes it attach to itself. To
be more precise,
glucosamine itself
doesn't play any role in fundamentally treating our joint pain. No
one can remove the fundamental root of arthritis, but
leptin, which was causing the arthritis,
acts like a powerful magnet and
pulls it out by binding to itself,
so the pain is reduced.
Oh, leptin sticks less to my joints,
causing inflammation.
In that sense, arthritis is not
exactly like rheumatoid
arthritis, which
is an autoimmune disease where the body attacks the joints. It
's not like that, literally.  Osteoarthritis is caused by overuse of the joints
due to over-exploitation of cotton, excessive use of rice farming, and
insufficient food intake, resulting in joint damage. The
pain is caused by bones rubbing against each other, and the
inflammation is due to the oleic acid.
Therefore, joint pain is not
caused by an autoimmune reaction of the body attacking leptin.
Furthermore, glucosamine
has no effect on any retriever.
Glucosamine does not cure arthritis. It
only prevents the bear from digging up the cleats,
so it is
not a fundamental treatment.
In that sense, I think it is
only right to remove the friend that is causing the pain rather than taking glucosamine to relieve the pain.
So, it doesn't really matter. I'm
hungry. If you eat a lot of mackerel, your teeth will hurt,
but
there will be an improvement. Um, was mackerel the only one that worked? Didn't
it really work when you ate a lot of meat? If
you eat a lot of it, it contains
all sorts of minerals, so
of course it's good for your teeth, but it also
has a lot of vitamin D and vitamin
A.
Yes, now.  I'm
not sure if it has to be mackerel or not. And
compared to other common chojeongs, there's
less Kate, so I don't think it's particularly good for dental health. Since
the company's sales are not great and it's a crying fit,
can I come? I'm not sad, I'm
not stressed, but I
use it for more than 30 minutes because of hip gout.
What is this?
I don't know. It's common to cry a lot. I've never heard of symptoms like this.
Oh, I think it can make you depressed, but
that's not true. Sob, sob. I do
n't know about the disclosure. Do you
keep doing it or
did it once?
Hello, Taeyoung. There is a
possibility that leaks, thyroid disease, and hepatitis can also be autoimmune diseases. If
strict Khan is
good, what would it be to eat less of it as a food to calm your thoughts? I'm going to
eat pastor hunting. If you
think about autoimmunity, what is Khan?
To control the speed of excretion of Osan point, you
have to eat the situation again. This is an example.
First,
when you eat this, it
would be good to find a sulfuric acid sauce that will burn your body as little as possible.
It's the same,
and if you eat a lot of food, it's okay to
eat a lot of it, so if you think it's not a big problem,
eating something like sweet potatoes is okay.
If you think it's better to eat a little more,
turmeric isn't bad either.
Turmeric is a real oxalate bomb, so you can
eat just a little bit to the point where you can stop. It's
temporary, but this is filling up about 2g of familiarity, so if
you fill up about
60mg, you'll probably eat about 2g and fill up 60mg. You
can also add a little bit of seasoning to your regular food like this.
The situation is probably just eating the strong stuff
itself, so you
won't absorb much of the other bad things.
But I don't know much about coats.
Autoimmune diseases are about
not knowing exactly what the body reacts to in a plant, so it
's a sudden, scalding approach to nutrition.
There are all kinds of toxins in plants, but
most of them we don't know exactly.
I'm particularly sensitive to them, so I
don't know exactly what they are, so I'll
just
stop eating them and try to
cleanse my body.  That's right,
now there's a principle like that,
and of course,
by eating a lot of meat, you get all the nutrients
your body needs to heal and
recover. And
anyway,
since it's not clear what's causing the problem in the body, I think it's best to
add the form one by one while protecting Khan and
seeing how your body reacts. And
temporarily stopping by adding 60mg is
really just a temporary
stop, so you can only know that
it was really because of the 4 years of Oksa. If you
want to control the speed by eating consistently, you need to eat more.
In the Tri-LOL Eight group, people who were eating
more than 1000mg a day for 5% of their waist size and
really eating a no-brainer diet are recommended to
reduce it by 5% a week. You
need to eat more.
My husband's neutral fat level didn't go down during exercise, and he's been on a part-
time job for 10 months.
In May, the test showed 130, in
April 156, and in June 132.
First, rest when you get tested.  You fasted for at least
12 hours,
right? You need to fast for more than 12 hours before
taking the coffee test.
And don't you eat cold foods? It's
not like you don't eat anything because you don't shiver. What are
some good foods to eat during exercise?
Will it help us? I'm
taking salt and iron during
exercise. It's not good to not eat while exercising.
Generally, it's better to
exercise on an empty stomach and eat after exercising. What's the
reason for the sunburn?
Well,
now,
other things like that, getting a lot of sunlight
helps with vitamin D production and depression.
Likewise, this mental
acupuncture helps with stability and things like that, so you
can see it a lot. I'm not
sure what it would be like if it weren't for that. They
say that not having enough can cause depression. Can you find a product when you have a bad disability? If you eat wild darts, it's all good. As I mentioned earlier,
eating too much oily seafood is not good,
but that does exist.
Water is harder to digest, so
seafood is better.
There are quite a few people who say their physical condition is not so good. Perhaps because
we humans only recently
started eating seafood, it feels like our bodies are not accustomed to it
compared to eating meat.
In that sense, when I eat seafood, my
body doesn't feel all that good. I
mainly eat raw fish, beef, and
lamb.
But if you're
comfortable eating people and want to be healthy,
eating all kinds of fish is fine. However, it's
much better to eat things that you can eat, including the internal organs. In particular,
crustaceans and shellfish are
much more nutritious.
They also have a lot of vitamin D.
Since farmed fish is often
touted as being wild-caught, it's naturally better.
Shellfish,
even if farmed, are raised by
feeding them and attaching them to their bodies,
so that's not bad. I have a
cold, a runny nose, and
intermittent upper abdominal pain. Will
taking organ meats for 5 days help? I
have no appetite, so I haven't eaten popcorn yet.
Yes, when I'm sick, fasting
isn't bad. They
say that long-acting oils
help with that. It seems to be a viral infection, so you
can see this point when you have a disability. A
common prescription would be to try a megadose of Tammy AB.
That's a natural way to do it. Trying the
Russian way, really intensely, would be
good. If you can,
try a sauna. A half-body bath is the longest I can endure, and I'm submerged in hot water. If you can even remove cotton salt, that would be even better. If that doesn't work, a cold shower would be helpful.
4.2
Rush. First, I
put some raw garlic in my shoulder, and then I
hit the guys who came right in. I
go into the sauna and
fight until I'm about to die, until I'm shivering and shriveled.
Then I immediately
throw myself into the ice bath. They
say it cures everything right away.
Just hearing about it makes me freak out, but I forget about the cold and
it's okay.
This extreme home system.  You
do it, you drink alcohol,
eat
garlic, go to the sauna, take a
cold shower, take a bath, and so on. If you
have the stamina to back it up with home sis,
I think it's a good method.
Just take a cold and look, and you'll
immediately break the buffet road.
When you have an ulcer,
eating old cucumbers can help you run a race, but
this year, I ate a cucumber and my condition
got worse. I
caught norovirus while eating it, but I
don't want to eat fertilizer.
Dogae Rio means that you
shouldn't get norovirus if you
cook it thoroughly. Norovirus itself seems to be a hero that only unhealthy people get. If you cook it thoroughly, it should be okay.
But if you
don't want to eat it, there's nothing you can do.
Dogs and
crabs are processed these days.
Crabs are delicious, so if you eat them like this, you
eat the intestines too.
Those are good too.
Each noddle like Seowoon is also good.
4 If you sit down on clams, you
can eat them whole from head to toe.
Things like smelt are also good.  It's good.
You fasted, and ate two meals of
white rice, not less than half a bowl, and some
fruit. What about
neutral fat? Did you have any other tests? What was your fasting insulin level? Was your fasting blood sugar high? It would be good to check your insulin level. It's almost all about the height of the fallen angel, so you can go and check it after seeing the main character. Eating rabbit without flying is the boss,
but I don't think it's that much. I'll see if you can
hear more about exercising in the flood.
Instead of
eating two meals of white rice, not less than half a bowl, you can try eating
one meal of flying. It would be good to get a fasting insulin test. I heard that
people who have been drinking shouldn't go into hot water. Is that
okay? Then, no, I'm not drinking a lot. I
just
drink one shot of vodka. It's
not like you drink a lot with a garlic clove in a teacup. That's the sound.
Of course, if you give yourself a high level of vodka,
even with that shot, the alcohol will
be quite high.
Um,
so now we
talk about eating broccoli and omegas.
Sseol Propane, and then the West,
while eating plant-based foods, if we
look at it, the superiors or the effects are ultimately
reduced, and it always causes me, but the
exact same mechanism occurs when we smoke or
drink alcohol.
2 The problem is the dosage.
Eating broccoli or something plant-based is
awkward. It's good. Beyond that, what about
eating something with a ballpoint pen? What did you eat? Sseol Propane?
That's a blessing. Now, the body's oxidative stress
goes down like this. Our body's way of detoxifying those things.
It's exactly the same as before. So
if you can eat it in an appropriate amount, you
can cause comedones.
Literally, so vodka shots
aren't that salty. So, if you take it like that, and
take vitamin A, the absorption
pathway is the only way to detoxify
it. In the case of alcohol, there
's something in common. So if you eat a lot of tools,
vitamin A isn't absorbed.
4 If you look at the actual appropriate dosage, it
's really not much. If you eat a little, you
can absorb much more vitamin A.
But
there are things like that.
In this way, it's better to
eat it in moderation like this. It's
not much, as you might think.  It's not like that when you go into the ground with it, so the
epigastric area hurts.
Is there inflammation here? When you
see a cold virus and it's causing a fuss, sometimes your stomach
hurts like that, so if the
epigastric area is pulled out, there's no second chance.
First, would
n't it be better to fast for a while and gain some time? In fact, after resting for a few days and hugging and
staying warm under the blanket, wouldn't it get better?
Try eating some of that. There are clay and charcoal
powders. Try eating some. It'll
help. It's
not colostrum.
Ah, I think it'd be good to have a corner these days, but
there are a lot of people. Do I have to do it all? I
use it a lot on TV every day, so I
can't catch it even if I wanted to.
Rather than Park Seok, I'm alone, so
if I catch it, it'll go up. They recognize it for 6 months, right? It would be
good to get the vaccine and quickly catch the coronavirus and go around with those antibodies. I
think raising each cortex is the best. I'll do it. Nothing will happen.
* In front of the hospital 0 days. You shouldn't eat it every day, right?
Ah
* Ice fish and salted [ __ ] roe have that much oil.
Both are not a lot, so I think it's okay to eat them every
day. My
fasting blood sugar is 90 and my insulin is 6.74. I've reached
the point where I can reach the sex
hormones. My
insulin is 6.7 for 3 days, which is a little high, but my
fasting insulin
is 2,673, which is
below o. If you feel like your
sincerity has not yet recovered 100%, it's
better to eat them all at once rather than reducing the amount of one thing.
Eating one meal in the room air
might not be bad, or it might
be better to eat one meal in the airplane.
Of course, it's good to exercise, and
of course, you have to put in the reagent oil.
Yes, and it's important to sleep well and
have good lifestyle habits. So, for the
sincerity,
whether it's because of the blue light or not, if you
can't sleep well, the white
paper results are high, and
Lee Soon-jung and Sunny continue to get worse. It's
hard because the results are getting better. If you
continue to eat the oil,
there won't be any major problems with cancer. If you
eat well,
the level will be high even after eating.  Your stomach can hurt like crazy.
If your intestines are bad, that can happen.
So, even if there's nothing like Berry Berry Nina,
these things that have antibacterial and antifungal properties are extremely toxic.
Just because they're natural foods doesn't mean they're okay. There are
poisonous plants and mushrooms, and things like
that. If we eat those things,
we might not die,
but we might kill
bacteria.
In that sense, it
's not always that good, so I
think it's often more beneficial to first create an intestinal environment.
Rather than trying to kill them, it's better to eat
small amounts, have
good lifestyle habits,
cut out
a lot of pretense, and go for a walk outside.
Changing your intestinal flora is
n't limited to food. Since
nutritional supplements are supplements, it
's not just about what you eat.
Increasing contact with animals,
going outside and sunbathing a lot,
and going for
walks in the wild
all have a huge impact.
Being single, going to bed and waking
up on time,
eating regular meals, intermittent fasting, and all of
these things are also important in your lifestyle.
There are so many influences, so it would
be especially helpful to do those things first. If you
keep eating things that are trying to kill you,
the cuts are very toxic to our body. If you
have arteriosclerosis, the hypertrophy
has decreased by 0.15mm. The arteriosclerosis half
exists in the 1.8th percentile. The
calcium habit in Wangsang neighborhood came out. If the calcium score of the product is
very low, it is
calculated, and
there is still experience with arteries, but
in the West, it is the Kasim score. I don't
think you have to worry too much at that time. If you
continue to fight well,
shouldn't it be okay?
And I don't know if you've
had your vitamin D levels checked,
but if your wife has had a lot of tests, it would be
good to eat well. This
is very important in producing this.
Now, when you take vitamin D, it
is important for other Fiji spiritualities to burn,
but if you get it, you die.
However, when I used Angola,
people who were fiery got coronavirus, the axis
point.
So, in the past, in the United States, there were a lot of things like that.
You know, there were a lot of
things like parties, and first, they
gave out prize money only to those who got COVID-19, and they also
raised COVID-19 together. At that time, if you look at it, it was like, "Sol," especially, I understand what their intentions were, but they did that a lot. I think that layer should have done that to quickly get COVID-19. This wasn't done by forcing them to hit the key points.
Can't you buy beatboxing cheaply without a business number? 4. If you don't have a business number, you ca
n't buy it cheaply.
Now, any business number really
doesn't matter. Real estate rental business
doesn't matter. 5. Even
if it has nothing to do with meat, a shoe
store doesn't matter. But you
have to have at least one thing.
Yes, you have to report your business.
I saw a plant channel a while ago that each YouTuber has, and Khan said that it
has been possible for 8 years.
So, my current diet is a lot of elasticity and I'm
interested in moon food. I heard that it's
similar to classical music, and they're doing
experiments to see what effect it has on our body. There's
no atmosphere. But I heard that the
liver and gallbladder fight through some mechanism. Whether it's
because of the fat or the biosynthesis at the time, each individual's body.  It depends on the restaurant,
but I
'm worried that Cisco might be overdoing it this year.
Ah, but now, when people talk about their physical condition,
many of them talk based on their own guesses, so it's a bit difficult.
Well, I
think that's probably because it's not easy to do that in the US. Because
hospital fees are so expensive, it's not easy to get tested,
right? I thought about it.
In our country, if you have denture insurance,
of course, not all dental clinics will cover it, but you
can still get tested within a reasonable range. Is it because
the prices in the US are too expensive to get
tested? Frank always said he
thought he had something, but it turned out to be nothing.
So, as far as I remember, the
last thing he said was, "It's
just because of the iron." It's not a good idea to
try to control your diet with iron and other things, like a dream.
There are many reasons, but anyway,
out of the total iron intake in my body, even if
I eat 100g of meat,
it's not much. I think it's because my
metabolism is better here.  It's also
very important to eat plenty of liver, which contains vitamin A and iron.
I
have a condition called 8x hematemesis, which is a disease that causes a huge amount of iron accumulation. It's not genetic, but if you
look at the iron gate, it continues to be excessive.
Eating liver doesn't work, and if it
keeps rising, you ca
n't reduce the iron intake. You can just do a blood transfusion. You can just draw some blood.
Oh, the iron and frostbite have expanded.
So, I guess it wasn't iron.
So, before that, I
said, "We'll do our part," and then I told him to
come. But in the end, it was all my
guesses. I don't do tests. I just
guess later. So,
when Frank said he was sick,
there wasn't much concrete data, so I don't think he talked much about
iron and iron. But if he
really talked that much, I
think he did an actual parity test. I'm
not sure.
Anyway, if I have too much iron in my body, you
can just draw some blood. My
vitamin D is 146.
mg putty sol l,
right? So, that's what we usually
do in Korea.
Earlier, 30 were deficiencies, and from 30 to
62 were
appropriate. If this confession exceeds that, it's considered excessive.
Isn't that right? Page 144 is too
much. Page 43 is vitamin D. It
seems like Tang Wei or Kate are likely to have a deficiency in episode 143, 1p.
Did you also get tested for urinary tract
infections? No, it seems like they're resting. Too much vitamin D can cause calcium to not be absorbed properly, which can be bad for your vascular health. If Taemin has that much, the risk of kidney stones and arteriosclerosis increases. My
husband hates drinking milk, so should
n't he eat it?
When he drank more, it was fine. It's
because you adapt. When you
don't drink milk and when you eat meat, the
gut flora is so different that it takes time for someone who didn't drink
milk to change to someone who continues to drink milk.
4. Yes, this is a bit ambiguous. If you're going to drink milk in the cabinet,
this adaptation period is meaningful.
For example, if you drink it only once a week,
or once a month, you need to
eat it consistently for that to happen.  It's
a bit tricky to get used to it, and it goes back.
If you drink it for a long time, it's
a bit tricky. You
can also test vitamin A, but if you
go later and check, that vitamin,
first of all, if vitamin D is that high, you shouldn't
give it.
Then, there are a lot of team, and the
fragrance is
KT and versi, so
I don't know what Frank does these days. Actually, I'm not really interested.
Oh, when I saw it before, the
most recent time I saw Frank was when
he was doing "Where's a Day?" and he
uploaded a picture of the restaurant he was eating at, right?
In that book, the second
part, when Khan was dieting, he uploaded a picture of the overview. The
most recent thing I saw was a
story about clothes. It's a bit old. I think I saw it a while ago.
Part 5
problem. Park Seon-jeong's height is nano. The
last time I saw it, it
was all gone. Sometimes, the
tail, but then he put a lot of barley in it and
boiled it, and
then he put in venison or something like that, and he
scooped us up in it, and he
boiled a lot of barley and made something similar to our week and
ate it.
But he didn't work for the company or just
5 leptin.  I've
made so many videos about this, but how
can you just pull out barley and eat it without any pretreatment?
Yes, yes, a little.
And I remember that too.
Frank Ichisan must have made a few videos on phytate. It
wasn't Korea,
but he uploaded a video like this. I
saw that video. There was a similar video by Frank
Pitt. There was a comment saying that
meat has too much of a certain mineral, and
that it can be overconsumed, so
for example, iron.
Eating it with phytate
can prevent iron from becoming excessive.
So, people in the past must have intentionally eaten
phytate to prevent iron and iron deficiency.
And Frank replied by saying that
we can't combine certain minerals by eating phytate.
We can't control the
absorption of minerals that are in excess by eating phytate. Does
that make
sense?
So I nodded after seeing that.
But after talking about cheap things like that, I
saw him digging up barley and eating it. What's wrong?  I should say that
Shin-i's health has dropped significantly. I'm
starting to think that he's no longer trustworthy. White
blood cell counts
vary widely, including neutrophils and
eosinophils.
When each is deficient, the
suspected symptoms vary. If
there's too much of something, it could be reduced,
or if there's too much of something, it could be
a virus. I don't remember the exact arrangement, but for example, if there's a deficiency of 5, it could be a severe viral infection.
If there's a deficiency of 9, it could be
bacteria. If there's a deficiency of 1, it could be
parasitic. So, the suspected symptoms would vary slightly. But now, when there's a situation where we need a lot of white blood cells for our performance, we could use Blur Tool. But this could be a deficiency only when we haven't tested it, and it's difficult to know everything with a one-time test.
This person is sensitive and
prone to stress, so he gets nervous easily,
needs sleep, and has many days when the quality of sleep is poor.
Modern society itself is a
stressful environment, even in the past, when it was natural. Considering
this changing environment and special
personality, even
if you have a good diet, it's easy to get sick, so it's better to add supplements.
Are there any nutrients that would be helpful if I took them in?
Well,
if you get enough stress and such, Aegis 7 is not good either.
First of all, it is essential to maintain good lifestyle habits. When you wake up in
the
morning, get sunlight with your naked eyes, and before going to bed, 2 or 3 hours, or even 2 hours is a bit much. The reason I did it is to try my best if possible. And now, as you get closer to yourself, I also get better. Avoid exposure to blue light, keep the same amount of time, and for sleep hygiene,
create a routine before going to bed,
such as meditating. It is
very important to consistently do things like eating and drinking outside of meals.
5.
Now, with the changed environment, the
work we do has decreased, and the time we sweat and are in contact with the sun has
decreased. When we come, we get light and
sunbathe, and when we
sunbathe,
we change jobs. It's
not just about getting what we want at lunchtime.
For example, from sunrise to sunset, the
sunlight is different.
Oh, of course, you may not know this now, but
sunlight is different because it's different.  The
thing about light is that
when the Earth's atmosphere is like this, it
doesn't always shoot out at the same angle, but as
the Earth rotates, the
thickness of the atmosphere keeps increasing, so it
penetrates as the sun goes down. That's why we
can see the sun with our naked eyes during sunrise and sunset, but when the sun
rises brightly, it looks like a dull ray when we look at it with our eyes, and that's
because of the stairs and things like that.  In this way,
our body can feel the changes in sunlight with our skin and eyes. If
we go to extremes like this,
if we just block out the blue light with our eyes, we
can just wear contact lenses. But there are
things in our eyes that can detect this blue light.
So
protecting only our eyes is
not a solution. But
if we talk about this the other way around, when our body is
in a sleeping state, it is
constantly
exposed to the changing sunlight. We
still feel it with our bodies,
but now, when we
don't have that, we
don't receive that light anymore. We
live in bright places even after the sun sets, and we
continue to receive blue light, especially white gum.
These things are also increasing. As our lifestyle habits change, it
becomes more and more difficult to endure such things.
So, it's important to do our
best in the areas where we can.
And it's
much the same.
Now, while doing all that,
there are definitely things you can try in addition.
[Music]
It would be good to take some acne supplements.
If you come to Pyeongtaek with the whole idea in mind, you
can look younger.
Now, it's better for me.
New life. Magnesium. Ah, this is the
country. Now, you
can also take some Clysine supplements. Before going to bed, especially, Afly
C is this amino acid. If you
eat a lot of meat, you can take a lot of collagen, which is your specialty. You can't take it,
but you
can try taking more.
Or, you can take some Google before going to bed.
Clysine is a neurotransmitter that helps our body's ache
and brain to relax and rest
comfortably. You
can supplement Clysine with it. Melatonin is needed to sleep well at night.
Melatonin is made from serotonin, and
serotonin needs tryptophan, so
tryptophan is also a
key ingredient. Eat
soup about once a day.  There are ways to help
tryptophan enter the brain more easily by eating some.
In the same sense, you
can try this, similar to Klein.
4. Klein, if you
consistently take magnesium supplements, it
might work. Tryptophan, which you
might try today, is similar to
Ceres. It blocks it, so you
might have more test scores and things like that.
Now, it's also very important for relieving tension and other things in the body. You probably
mentioned supplements in your head.
You might try taking something like magnesium. It's
not good to take too much at once, so eat it
like food. It won't be absorbed
anyway, so if you don't eat it with food,
it'll be sensitive. If you eat it wrong, you might get a stabbing
response. I happened to eat ginger and raw chestnuts, and it felt
good.
Seeing you stay up all night every day makes me feel better and stronger. I
don't know what part of the night makes me feel better. I
always think that 1 year olds make it in their bodies, so D
Carter Race Clutch One was the most powerful. I
need to eat meat well.
Glutathione, as I mentioned earlier, is
hundreds of times more powerful than all that nonsense. It
's past 10 o'clock.
I'm finishing up the drinking broadcast and getting
ready to go to bed. Ah,
like this. Today at 4 o'clock, I
had a light lunch today. I usually
eat a lot. Yes, I had a
light lunch today. This is it. I probably
ate enough calories,
but I
only ate Korean rice. Hoho,
compact.
What 2.
Ah, after eating all of this, I ate this
yogurt, whey,
2 yogurts, and
a little bit of yogurt, so I think I'm
lacking in calories or something.
Anyway, if I eat like that, I
feel like I'm not full.
Dinner too.
Yes, especially since I ate this,
I think I'll be hungry tomorrow morning.
But it's a bit hard to eat right now,
so
I
'd appreciate it.
Ace 1st item. Yesterday's ingredients: minerals,
protein, vitamin p,
glutathione, glutathione
[music]
4. Glutathione 2.
So, you can ingest it directly
like this.
If you have any unexpected requests for dairy products that you haven't found, please check out the
Clutch Sister's
Blur. Since you can consume it directly like this,
other than the whey, what else is there? Raw egg,
egg white, uncooked egg white &
clutch paper.
4 Anyway, thank you for watching. Please
stop by once in a while. It
will be broadcast again next week. I
'm really trying to upload the nose, but
5.
First of all,
I'll go and look at my bangs as much as possible. If I were to upload it,
someone would have to go up to Duffy and hold a
flower. I'm worried about that. I have to
upload it alone, but
there's no mugwort that I dragged alone.
There are many things that I can't do alone, so what
should I do? Eunya, I'm worried about this. I'll think about it a bit and
broadcast it on the lung cancer team's cancer site.
Lutein, Zea, Jang Cain, production 2.
It's good to eat it together with your parents.